MRS. WOLOWITZ: What's going on?
Are you boys roughhousing?
(Howard:)We're just talking, Ma.
(Howard's mother:)If you don't settle down right now...
...I'm not gonna let you
have any more sleepovers.
(Howard:)For God's sake, Ma, I'm 27 years old.
And it's not even a school night!
- Comfy now?
- Eh...
(Sheldon:)That poster of Halle Berry
is a little unnerving.
(Howard:)So don't look at it.
- She's like my fourth favorite Catwoman.
- No kidding?
Yeah, Julie Newmar, Michelle Pfeiffer,
Eartha Kitt and then her.
- What about Lee Meriwether?
- Oh, I forgot about Lee Meriwether.
(Howard:)Well, I'm glad that's settled.
(Sheldon:)That makes Halle Berry
my fifth favorite Catwoman.
Julie Newmar, Michelle Pfeiffer,
Eartha Kitt, Lee Meriwether...